Scarlett S. Verheul

I am a lifelong programmer and tech enthusiast with over 12 years of industry experience, primarily in development roles focused on SaaS and internal company projects. I believe in using the right tool for the job, with a particular emphasis on backend development and hardware/OS integration. My expertise lies in non-cloud "bare metal"/"VPS" Linux environments

Personal Information

Location: Capelle aan den IJssel / Randstad / Netherlands (*CEST* +2)

Citizenship: Nederlands **Date Of Birth**: 14-02-1994

Email: scarlett.verheul@gmail.com

Github: <u>ScarlettSamantha</u> **LinkedIn**: <u>ScarlettVerheul</u>

Key: https://scarlettbytes.nl/gpg

Employment Type:

Full Time | Remote/Hybrid

EXPERIENCE

I3D.net, Capelle aan den IJssel — Infrastructure Software Engineer

Sept 2021 - PRESENT

Domain: Hosting, Network Automatisation, Networking

At I3D I worked on maintaining and improving/rebuilding various production systems focusing on server infrastructure and automated server provisioning/network automation and processing raw data gathered from telemetry into a workable application.

I also worked on the D&I team to improve equity and access to every employee.

Digivotion B.V., Rotterdam — *Tech Lead*

Feb 2019 - Sep 2021

Domain: SaaS, Devops, PHP, Code Rework, Modernization

At Digivotion I worked on improving and developing parts of the SAAS systems offered to customers, I worked on the backend and filled a day to day technical leadership role. I also worked on improving the developer experience by migrating away from aging infrastructure to newer systems.

Supportdesk B.V., Rotterdam — Software Engineer | Development/Incidents-CERT

Aug 2016 - Feb 2019

Domain: Development-AAS, Webplatform (E-Commerce), CERT

My time at supportdesk mostly focused on implementing direct (semi-)custom wishes of customers into their web applications. I also worked on the CERT/Security incidents teams for when a customer had an security incident/hack on a server. I also worked on improving the performance and scaling from customers on their platforms.

SKILLS (1 ... 5)

PHP5/7/8(5),
Python3(4), Git (4),
Linux-Debish-Cent(↑ 3),
Laravel/Eloquent(3), CI/CD(3),
Pipelines(3), MySQL (3), Microservice
(3), Docker(3), Flask(3), Rabbitmq (3),
K8's(2), Micropython(2), PostgreSQL(2),
Django(2), PL/Python(2), C# (2),
Pure/jQuery Javascript (2), NumPy (2),
Bash(2),
Game Dev(1)

Other Skills (/Buzzwords):

Rest(full) - Scrum/Agile - Waterfall
- Multithreading (Python, Not PHP)
- Elasticsearch - Jira/Atlassian(②) Performance Optimisation Github/Gitlab - SNMP - Unit
Test/PyTest OOP - Xdebug - DDD - Netbox Cacti - Documentation - DNS DHCP - IP - Networking - TCP/IP
Suite - Swagger - OpenApi - I18N LibreNMS - Markdown - XML JSON - Logging - Sentry - SAAS Peer-review(MR's) - D&I
Computer/Server - Internal
Hardware

Helloprint, Drukzo, Rotterdam — Team Lead IT

July 2015 - Aug 2016

Domain: Startup, Quick Iteration, PHP, External API's

Here I worked on Improving the internal and external platform and implementing new systems. I also worked on creating a team to share the workload and facilitate that. I also worked on integrating various external API's

[Skipped 2 experiences (available on linkedin)]

Drecomm B.V, Rotterdam — PHP Developer

Sept 2012 - Aug 2014

Domain: Project Development, PHP, B2B, Typo3, Drupal

I worked on improving customers' applications with new features or bug fixes or installations. I also worked with different teams to help out when extra developers were needed.

Here I started to specialize more into the server/backend parts of the job.

[Skipped 1 experiences (available on <u>linkedin</u>)]

PROJECTS(ABSTRACT) / AREAS OF WORK

Linux/Network -

Having used linux as my primary Os for years now I am very comfortable in the unix env and am used to working with servers remote or locally via cli or programmatically. And am a believer in the (FL)-OSS movement.

PHP Development -

I have worked on various projects ranging from saas to internal company needs. This was most of the time combined with updating/improving existing production code bases. I worked here with diverse frameworks mostly Laravel/Eloquent(>4) and a bit Symfony and Zend(1) over the years

Python Development -

Python has been my goto language when working on projects where more performance was needed (due to php not having threading, at least till v8) and/or more os integration. It's my personal favorite language and most of my private projects are written in it. I prefer pure python with libs and objects from things that I need and for more complex projects flask/django

Workflow -

I prefer to work in a waterfall/scrum/agile environment working with a task/ticket management tool with a git based workflow on a remote git server. In a good D(/O)TAP process with pipelines managing development and versioning.

EDUCATION

Grafisch Lyceum, Rotterdam — Application/Web Developer

Aug 2010 - Feb 2012 (Finished in 1.5 years instead of normal 4)

I followed the application developer post secondary program, I received my degree in a hastened way due to finishing all the degree work early.

HOBBIES/INTERESTS

Traveling, MicroElectronics, HPC, Programming, AI, Pets, Technology, Foreign Relations, Global Politics, Current Affairs, Space, Airsoft, 3D Printing, Warhammer 40K, Gaming(4x, Strategy)

LANGUAGES

Dutch | Mother Language English(C2) | Raised/Education Bilingual

REFERENCES

Available upon request please contact me.

NOTES

I choose to work only directly with companies or projects without recruiting agency's or complex middlemen.

I am open to work on Salary or ZZP(EN: Contractor)/Contract basis depending on the project and area.

This c.v. was handmade and as I am *dyslexic* it might contain spelling mistakes/errors.

If this C.V. was given to you by an external recruiter/recruiting agency, then this c.v has been harvested without my consent or approval.

SECURITY

This document has been <u>signed</u>(.sig file) with my <u>GPG key</u>. If it is not signed or a bad signature message is given upon verification, then this document has been modified without my permission.

Signing Key Fingerprint(s):

RSA4096[pub] 2F98 5406 3563 1EEC A083 5196 744D 7EC1 5F90